Lasting victories are won in the heart.
Heaven & Earth is a history, war, drama film directed by Oliver Stone.
In a small Vietnamese village torn apart by war, a young woman faces
unimaginable horrors before deciding to escape to the city.
There, she encounters a compassionate Marine who offers her hope and a chance
at a new life, igniting the possibility of a future together.
Eugenia, played by Debbie Reynolds.
Le Ly, played by Hiep Thi Le.
Steve Butler, played by Tommy Lee Jones.
Papa, played by Haing S. Ngor.
Mama, played by Joan Chen.
Uncle Luc, played by Thuan K. Nguyen.
Heaven & Earth is a 1993 American biographical war drama film written and
directed by Oliver Stone, and starring Tommy Lee Jones, Haing S.
Ngor, Joan Chen, and Hiep Thi Le.
It is the third and final film in Stone's Vietnam War trilogy, following
Platoon (1986) and Born on the Fourth of July (1989).
The film was based on the books When Heaven and Earth Changed Places and Child of War, Woman of Peace,
both authored by Le Ly Hayslip about her experiences during and after the Vietnam War.
It received mixed reviews and performed poorly at the box office.
The film explores themes of vietnam war, vietnam, war crimes, saigon, biography.
The tone is emotional.